Council on Foreign Relations Records: Studies Department Series, 1918-2004: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Subseries 3B: Records of Groups, 1918-1996; 91.12 linear feet 219 boxes
  - Post-1973 Study Groups, 1959-2005; 93 boxes (1 partial)
    - Latin American Program Breakfast Symposium on Argentina: a Follow-up on Economic Reform, 1992 December 7; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 14)
    - Working Group on United States Policy Toward Africa (First Meeting, 1992 December 15), 1992-1993, 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 15)
    - Africa Update Meeting with Barkan, Joel D., the Kenyan Elections and U.S. Foreign Policy, 1993 January 28; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 16)
    - Seminar on The European Community, Its Southeastern Flank, and the Issues of Enlargement, Tsoukalis, Loukas, 1993 February 1; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 17)
    - Study Group on US Policy Toward Asia, with the University of California Institute on Global Conflict and Cooperation (IGCC), 1993 March 11-12; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 18)
    - African Studies Seminar, Africa: Whose Continent is it Anyway?, Michaels, Marguerite, 1993 March 16; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 19)
    - Africa Update Meeting with Moussalli, Michel, Human Rights Conditions in Zaire, 1993 March 18; 1 folder (Box 289, Folder 20)
    - Latin American Program Breakfast Series, Latin America 1993 Items on the Agenda for the New Administration (First Meeting, 1993 March 17), 6 folders
      - Latin America 1993 Items on the Agenda for the New Administration, 1993 March 17, 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 1)
      - Economic Issues, 1993 March 31; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 2)
      - The Environment, Human Rights, and Drugs, 1993 April 14; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 3)
      - Population, Migration, and Economic Development, 1993 May 5; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 4)
      - Policy Options: Cuba and Haiti, 1993 May 19; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 5)
      - Policy Options: Central America, 1993 June 9; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - Africa Update Meeting with Nyati, Eugene, South Africa in the Year, 2000; 1993 April 19; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - European Studies Workshop on Spain in the 1990s Prospects and Dilemmas on the Eve of the General Elections, 1993 May 3, 2 folders
      - Workshop, 1993; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 8)
      - Book, The New Spain, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 9)
    - Workshop on Argentina's Economic Reforms: Prospects and Implications, with The Argentine Council on Foreign Relations, 1993 June 14; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 10)
    - Africa Update Meeting with Bourdes-Ogouliguende, Jules-Aristide, Democratization in Gabon, 1993 June 14; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 11)
    - Economic Studies Seminar on U.S.-E.C. Relations: GATT Gridlock and Regional Preoccupations, 1993 June 16; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 12)
    - African Studies Seminar on The Future of U.S./South African Economic Relations, 1993 June 28; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 13)
    - Roundtable Luncheon for Adedeji, Adebayo, The Prospect for Africa's Second Liberation, 1993 September 14; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 14)
    - African Studies Seminar on South Africa in Transition: Social and Economic Development, 1993 September 21; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 15)
    - Congressional Symposium on South Africa: Toward a Democratic Future, with the House Committee on Africa, 1993 September 30; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 16)
    - The Saudi Financial and Economic Situation Studies Seminar, 1993 October 4; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 17)
    - Studies Program Seminar for U.S. Army War College Students, The Middle East after the Israeli-Palestinian Agreement and The Changing Character of American Foreign Policy, 1993 October 12; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 18)
    - Dinner Discussion on Economic Development Programs in the West Bank and Gaza, 1993 October 28; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 19)
    - Study Group on Cuba's Future; Prospects and Dangers – An Examination of U.S. Policy Options (First Meeting, 1993 October 28), 5 folders
      - First Meeting, 1993 October 28; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 20)
      - Second Meeting, The Domestic Foreign Policy Nexus: Cuba in Miami and Washington, 1993 November 18; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 21)
      - Third Meeting, The Cuban Economy After the Cold War, 1993 December 2; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 22)
      - Fourth Meeting, Policy Options, 1993 December 16; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 23)
      - Fifth Meeting, Findings by Members of the Delegation: Council of American Ambassadors Research Mission to Cuba, 1994 April 28; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 24)
    - Africa Update Meeting with Mkhondo, Rich, Reporting South Africa, 1993 November 10; 1 folder (Box 290, Folder 25)
    - Mexico Group Roundtable (First Meeting, 1993 November 10), 2 folders
      - Background Paper for Meeting, 1993 November 10; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 1)
      - Seminar, The Economic Impact of NAFTA, Realities and Politics: What are the Facts?, 1993 December 8; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - European Program Study Group on The Problems of Governance and Democracy in the West (First Meeting, 1993 November 18), 7 folders
      - General, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 3)
      - Meetings, 1993 November 18-1994 June 14; 6 folders
        - Meeting 1, 1993 November 18; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 4)
        - Meeting 2, 1993 December 16; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 5)
        - Meeting 3, 1994 February 3; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 6)
        - Meeting 4, 1994 March 3; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 7)
        - Meeting 5, 1994 April 21; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 8)
        - Meeting 6, 1994 June 14; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 9)
    - Conference on Kosovo and the Balkans, 1993 December 7; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 10)
    - USIA-Sponsored Events, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 11)
    - Seminar on Iraq: Scenarios for the Future, 1994 January 19; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 12)
    - Africa Update Meeting on the South African Election, 1994 February 7; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 13)
    - Latin American Program and the Project on International Organizations and Law Joint Symposium on Regional Perspectives on Nuclear Non-Proliferation: The Latin American Case, 1994 February 14; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 14)
    - Africa Studies Seminar on the Question of Africa's Marginalization, 1994 February 18; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 15)
    - Latin American Program and Corporate Program Forthcoming Issues Seminar on Mexico, Issues in the Future of U.S.-Mexican Relations, 1994 February 24; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 16)
    - Luncheon on Economic Reform and Growth in Venezuela, 1994 March 11; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 17)
    - Latin American Program and European Program Joint Seminar on Britain and Europe, 1994 March 24; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 18)
    - Author's Review Group on Haass, Richard N., The Calculus of Force: U.S. Military Intervention in the Post-Cold War World, 1994 March 29; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 19)
    - International Economics and Finance Program on Economic Cooperation in the Asia-Pacific, Session One: Regional Perspectives on APEC, 1994 April 4; 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 20)
    - Study Group on the United States and the Persian Gulf (First Meeting, 1994 April 4), 1994, 1 folder (Box 291, Folder 21)
    - Latin American Program Breakfast Series on the PRI and the Elections: Consequences for U.S.-Mexican Relations, 1994 May 5; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Latin American Program, Corporate Program, and Meetings Department Breakfast, Presidential Series, A Conversation with Lula, 1994 May 12; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Latin American Program Breakfast with Aristide, Jean-Bertrand, 1994 May 13; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - Haitian Working Group (First Meeting, 1994 May 13), 1994, 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Africa Update Meeting on South Africa: Economic Reconstruction and Development, with Mboweni, Tito, 1994 May 19; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - African Studies Seminar on U.S, Policy Options in Zaire, 1994 June 1; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Symposium on Syrian in the "New" Middle East, 1994 June 6; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Africa Studies Seminar on "The Coming Anarchy" by Kaplan, Robert, 1994 June 16; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Special Edward R. Murrow Fellowship Seminar with Brady, Rose, Contemplating Kaptializm: A Contrarian View of Russia's Reforms, 1994 June 16; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 9)
    - Africa Update, South Africa: Strengthening Civil Society, with The Institute for Democracy in South Africa (IDASA), 1994 September 27; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 10)
    - John J. McCloy Workshop on the Strategic Goals of Czech Foreign Policy, 1994 October 4; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 11)
    - Studies Program Seminar for U.S. Army War College Students, 1994 October 11; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 12)
    - John J. McCloy Workshop on Slovenia After Independence, 1994 October 13; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 13)
    - Angola Update with Pacheco, Fernando, 1994 October 20; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 14)
    - Meeting on Italy and the United States: the View From Rome, 1994 October 21; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 15)
    - Iberian Seminar on Spain's Relation with the U.S. and Within Europe, 1994 October 24; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 16)
    - Naval War College Strategic Studies Group Symposium on International Environment –, 2005; 1994 October 25; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 17)
    - Middle East/North African Economic Summit convened by the Council on Foreign Relations and the World Economic Forum, Casablanca, Morocco, 1994 October 30-November 1; 5 boxes (2 partial)
      - Attendees, 1994; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 18)
      - Background Materials, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 19)
      - Conference Booklet/Program, 1994; 1 folder (Box 292, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, 1993-1995; 2 boxes (1 partial)
        - Funding, Planning, Invitations, 1994; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 1)
        - Invitations, 1994; 3 folders
          - Rejections, 1994; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 2)
          - Sent by Council on Foreign Relations, 1994; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 3)
          - Sent by World Economic Forum, 1994; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 4)
        - Jordan, 1994; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 5)
        - Memos and Descriptions, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 6)
        - Planning and Post-Conference, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 7)
        - Plenary, 1994; 2 folders (Box 293, Folder 8 to 9)
        - Report Mailings, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 10)
        - Requests for Fee Waivers, 1994; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 11)
        - Responses to Peterson Invitation, 1994; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 12)
        - Royal Air Maroc, 1994; 1 folder (Box 293, Folder 13)
        - Speakers, 1994; more than 2 folders
          - Acceptances/Confirmations, 1994; 2 folders (Box 294, Folder 1 to 2)
          - Pending, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 3)
        - Sughrue, Karen, Memos, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 4)
        - World Economic Forum, Original Faxes, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 5)
      - Council on Foreign Relations Conference Staff Lists, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 6)
      - Council on Foreign Relations/World Economic Forum Understanding and Guidelines, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 7)
      - Delegations, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 8)
      - Expert's Breakfast, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 9)
      - Final Declaration and Report Work, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 10)
      - Gelb, Les, Conference Materials, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 11)
      - Gulf State Participant Ideas, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 12)
      - Interactive Session Notes, 1994; 1 folder (Box 294, Folder 13)
      - Keller, Ken, Conference Materials, 1994; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 1)
      - Lists, 1994; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 2)
      - Media File, 1994; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 3)
      - Mid-East Helpers, 1994; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 4)
      - Morocco Logistics, 1994; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 5)
      - Participant Surveys, Completed, 1994; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 6)
      - Potential Corporations, 1994; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 7)
      - Program Planning, 1994; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 8)
      - Regional Lunches, 1994; 1 folder (Box 295, Folder 9)
      - Report Materials, 1994; 2 folders Two 3.5" Floppy Disks Included (Box 296, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Sessions, 1994; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 3)
      - Sponsors, 1994; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 4)
      - Steering Committee of the Middle East/North Africa Economic Summit, Second Meeting, 1994 October 17; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 5)
      - Trade and Project Exchange, 1994; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - European Studies Taskforce on NATO Expansion (First Meeting, 1994 December 5), 1994, 2 boxes (1 partial)
      - Background Papers, 1995; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 7)
      - Financial Information, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 8)
      - Invitations, 1994; 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 9)
      - Meetings, 1994 December 5, 1994 December 12, 1995 January 24, 1 folder (Box 296, Folder 10)
      - RAND Briefing, 1994 December 8; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 1)
      - Report, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 297, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Report Acceptances, 1995; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 4)
      - Report Briefing, 1995 April 26; 7 folders
        - Financials, 1995; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 5)
        - Meetings, 1995 April 26-May 15; 2 folders
          - Special Seminar, Should NATO Expand, Washington, D.C., 1995 April 26; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 6)
          - Meeting, Should NATO Expand, New York, 1995 May 15; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 7)
        - Planning, 1995; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 8)
        - Press Briefing, 1995; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 9)
        - Report Distribution, 1995; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 10)
        - Responses, 1995; 1 folder (Box 297, Folder 11)
    - Labor and the International Economy (First Meeting, 1995 January 9), 1994-1995, 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - John J. McCloy Workshop with Rieff, David, Journalism and Media Reporting in the Yugoslav Wars, 1995 April 24; 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 2)
  - Projects, 1918-1999; 49 boxes (1 partial)
    - War and Peace Studies (First Meeting, 1940 September 10), 4 boxes (2 partial)
      - Relations with State Department, 1940-1946; 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 3)
      - Territorial Group and Unbound Material, 1940-1944; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - 1940, 1 folder (Box 298, Folder 4)
        - Supplementary Materials, 1940; 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 1)
        - 1941, 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 2)
        - 1942, 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 3)
        - 1943, 1 folder (Box 299, Folder 4)
        - 1944, 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous Material on Regionalism, 1940-1943; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 2)
      - Economic and Financial Group and Unbound Material, 1941-1945; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 3)
      - Project Progress Reports, 1945; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 4)
      - Economic and Financial Group and Material of Interest, 1941-1944; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Material, 1940-1943; 1 folder (Box 300, Folder 6)
      - Council Questionnaire (draft), 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 1)
      - Selected Documents and Official Statements of United States Policy, 1918-1944; 2 folders
        - Volume 1, 1918-1943; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 2)
        - Volume 2, 1944; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - 1980s Project (First Meeting, 1974 May 2), 18 boxes (2 partial)
      - General, 1973-1980; portions of 2 boxes
        - Correspondence: Alphabetical by Council Member, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 4)
        - Descriptions, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 5)
        - "Desired Characteristics of an International Order", 1974 April; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 6)
        - Report to German Marshall Fund of US, 1975-1976 October 1; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 7)
        - Press Release, 1976 December 15; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 8)
        - Questions and Answers about Project, 1974 January; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 9)
        - Manning, Bayless, Speech to Council Directors- Project Proposal and Comments, 1973 September 10-October, 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 10)
        - "On Basic Assumption, Grand Rules and Constraints and Notes", 1974 April-1975 March; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 11)
        - Status Report, 1975 June-September; 1 folder (Box 301, Folder 12)
        - Status Reports, 1976-1980; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 1)
        - "White Series," First Paper, 1974 January; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 2)
        - "Values Goals Instrumental Norms, and Trails," by Ullman, Richard, Comments, 1974 March-April; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 3)
      - Finances/Foundations, 1972-1981; portions of 2 boxes
        - Budget Planning and Expenditures, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 4)
        - Budget Proposals, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 5)
        - Correspondence and Memos, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 6)
        - Early Project Budget Worksheets, 1974; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 7)
        - Final Financial Report, 1980; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 8)
        - Ford Foundation, 1973-1981; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 9)
        - German Marshall Fund, 1972-1981; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 10)
        - Honoraria, 1975-1980; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 11)
        - Lilly Endowment, Incorporated, 1973-1981; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 12)
        - Mellon Foundation, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 302, Folder 13)
        - Rockefeller Foundation, 1973-1981; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 1)
        - Fritz Thyssen Stiftung, 1975-1981; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 2)
      - Organization and Administration, 1973-1979; portions of 2 boxes
        - General Administrative Procedures, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 3)
        - Lists of Authors, Groups, Publications, etc, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 4)
        - General Correspondence with Miriam Camps, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 5)
        - Neal, Alfred Correspondence, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 6)
        - Conceptualization and Planning, 1973-1974; 2 folders
          - 1973, 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 7)
          - 1974, 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 8)
        - 1974 November Meetings, 2 folders
          - 1974 September-November, 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 9)
          - Papers Discussed, 1974; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 10)
        - Pre-Publication Distribution, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 303, Folder 11)
        - Relations with Board of Directors, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 1)
        - Relations with Committee on Studies, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 2)
        - Foreign Participation-General, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 3)
        - General Planning and Administration, 1975-1979; 4 folders
          - 1975, 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 4)
          - 1976, 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 5)
          - 1977-1979, 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 6)
          - Trips Abroad-Reports, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 7)
        - Working Group Membership and Organization (Staff Planning), 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 8)
      - Project Staff, 1974-1980; portions of 2 boxes
        - Consultants, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 9)
        - Diebold, William, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 10)
        - Editorial Staff (D-W), 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 11)
        - General, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 12)
        - Rapporteurs, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 13)
        - Recruitment of Staff and Authors, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 304, Folder 14)
        - Support Staff, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 1)
        - Farer, Tom, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 2)
        - Gompert, David, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 3)
        - Gwin, Catherine, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 4)
        - Hansen, Roger, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 5)
        - Lowenthal, Abraham, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 6)
        - Morse, Edward, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 7)
        - Ullman, Richard, 1976-1980; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 8)
      - Contacts, 1974-1979; portions of 2 boxes
        - US Institutions (alpha order), 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 9)
        - Non-US Institutions, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 10)
        - Relations with West and East German Institutes, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 11)
        - Relations with East European and USSR Institutions and Individuals, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 12)
        - Relations with China, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 13)
        - Relations with Japan, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 305, Folder 14)
        - Individuals, 1974-1979; 2 folders
          - A-K, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 1)
          - L-Z, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 2)
      - Authors, 1973-1979; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - General, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 3)
        - Adler-Karlsson, Gunnar on North-South Relations, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 4)
        - Arad, Uzi on Armed Conflict, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 5)
        - Barton, John on Nuclear Weapons, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 6)
        - Birnbaum, Norman Miscellaneous Paper, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 7)
        - Bull, Hedley on Armed Conflict, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 8)
        - Cahn, Anne on Armed Conflict, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 9)
        - Campbell, John on Human Rights, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 10)
        - Chace, James on Armed Conflict, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 11)
        - Cooper, Charles on Environmental/Global Commons/Economic Growth, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 12)
        - Dawkins, Peter on Armed Conflict, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 13)
        - Diaz Alejandro, Carlos, on North-South Relations, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 14)
        - Dominguez, Jorge on Human Rights, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 15)
        - Doyle, Michael on. Macroeconomic Policies and International Monetary Relations, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 306, Folder 16)
        - El-Mallakh, Ragaei on North-South Relations, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 1)
        - Enloe, Cynthia on Human Rights, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 2)
        - Fagen, Richard R. on North-South Relations, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 3)
        - Feiveson, Hal on Nuclear Weapons, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 4)
        - Fishlow, Albert on North-South Relations, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 5)
        - Garwin, Richard on Nuclear Weapons, 1973-1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 6)
        - Golay, Frank on North-South Relations, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 7)
        - Gordon, Lincoln on Independent Study, 1974-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 8)
        - Gordon, Robert on Macroeconomic Policies and International Monetary Relations, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 9)
        - Green, Stephen on International Disaster Relief, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 10)
        - Greenwood, Ted on Nuclear Weapons, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 11)
        - Hirsch, Fred on Macroeconomic Policies and International Monetary Relations, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 12)
        - Hoffman, Stanley on Independent Study, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 13)
        - Hollick, Ann on Environmental, Global Commons, Economic Growth, 1976-1979; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 14)
        - Isaacs, Harold R. on Autonomy and Identity, 1976; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 15)
        - Jequier, Nicholas Miscellaneous Paper, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 16)
        - Kruzel, Joseph on Armed Conflict, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 17)
        - Legum, Colin on Human Rights, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 307, Folder 18)